- Can I hear this record about
Rob Base and DJ E-Z Rock?
- Hey man, you sure you
wanna hear this, man?
You sure about that man?
All right
(upbeat music)
♪ Right about now ♪
♪ You're about to be possessed ♪
♪ By the sounds of ♪
♪ Emcee Rob Base and DJ E-Z Rock ♪
♪ Hit it ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ It takes two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to make it out of sight ♪
♪ Hit it! ♪ ♪ I wanna rock right now ♪
♪ I'm Rob Base and I came to get down ♪
♪ I'm not internationally known ♪
♪ But I'm known to rock the microphone ♪
♪ Because I get stupid,
I mean outrageous ♪
♪ Stay away from me if you're contagious ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the winner, no, not a loser ♪
♪ To be an emcee is what I choose-a ♪
♪ Ladies love me, girls adore me ♪
♪ I mean even the ones who never saw me ♪
♪ Like the way that I rhyme at a show ♪
♪ The reason why, man, I don't know ♪
♪ So let's go, 'cause ♪
♪ It takes two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to make it out of sight ♪
♪ Hit it! ♪
♪ My name is Rob, I gotta
real funky concept ♪
♪ Listen up, 'cause I'm
gonna keep you in step ♪
♪ I got an idea ♪
♪ That I wanna share ♪
♪ You don't like it,
so what, I don't care ♪
♪ I'm number one, the uno, I like comp ♪
♪ Bring all the suckers
'cause all them I'll stomp ♪
♪ Bold and black, but I will protect ♪
♪ All of my followers 'cause
all I want is respect ♪
♪ I'm not a doctor, put them in rapture ♪
♪ A slick brother that
can easy outfox ya ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Rob, the
last name Base, yeah ♪
♪ And on the mic, I'm
known to be the freshest ♪
♪ So let's start, it
shouldn't be too hard ♪
♪ I'm not a sucker so I
don't need a bodyguard ♪
♪ I won't fess, wear a bulletproof vest ♪
♪ Don't smoke Buddha,
can't stand sess, yes ♪
♪ It takes two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to make it out of sight ♪
♪ It take two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ Hit it! ♪
♪ The situation that the Base is in ♪
♪ I'm kinda stingy that's
why I don't wanna lend ♪
♪ A funky rhyme to a
foe or a good friend ♪
♪ But listen up 'cause I
want you to comprehend ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the leader,
the man, superior ♪
♪ I take care of ya and
then you get wearier ♪
♪ So just sit, my rhymes
are not counterfeit ♪
♪ The record sells which
makes this one a hit ♪
♪ It won't hurt to listen to Red Alert ♪
♪ Take off your shirt ♪
♪ Make sure it don't hit the dirt ♪
♪ I like the kids ♪
♪ The guys, the girls ♪
♪ I want the ducats 'cause
this is Rob Base's world ♪
♪ I'm on a mission, you
better just listen ♪
♪ To my rhymes 'cause I'm
all about dissin', 'cause ♪
♪ It takes two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to make it out of sight ♪
♪ Hit it! ♪
♪ I stand alone, don't need anyone ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Rob, just came to have fun ♪
♪ Don't need friends that act like foes ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Rob Base, the one who knows ♪
♪ About things that make you get weary ♪
♪ Don't cheer me, just hear me ♪
♪ Out, 'cause I got the clout, shout ♪
(crowd shouting)
♪ Before I turn the party out ♪
♪ I won't stutter ♪
♪ Project my voice, speak clearly ♪
♪ So you can be my choice
♪ ♪ On stage or on record ♪
♪ Go to the Wiz and select it ♪
♪ Take it off the rack,
if it's wack put it back ♪
♪ I like the Whopper, (beep) the Big Mac ♪
♪ If you want static, so let's go ♪
♪ So, throw up your hands ♪
♪ Go for what you know ♪
♪ Bro, I got an ego ♪
♪ Yo, talkin' to me, no, oh ♪
♪ 'Cause Rob is in the front,
EZ Rock is on the back up ♪
♪ We're not soft, so you
better just slack up ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm cool, calm
just like a breeze ♪
♪ Rock the mic with
the help of E-Z, Rock ♪
♪ On the set, the music plays ♪
♪ Only cuts the records that I say ♪
♪ It takes two to make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to make it out of sight ♪
♪ Aight, now, EZ Rock now,
when I count to three ♪
♪ I want you to get busy, you ready now? ♪
♪ One, two, three, get loose now! ♪
♪ It takes two to make a ♪
♪ It takes two to make ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ It takes two to ♪
♪ It takes two to make a thing ♪
♪ It takes two to make a ♪
♪ It takes, it takes,
it takes two to make a ♪
♪ It takes two to make a ♪
♪ It take, it takes, it
takes two to make a ♪